It's good.
Let's go!
– Let's go! – You're good, Mrka.
Good day.
ARRRGH!
Whoa!
Hi, all right!
Get back!
Hey!
Give it!
Please make Halleep's challenge líder!
From clumsy dances to Lasertots,
These bears could totally win an Oscar for comedy.
Well, I don't see a no bears allowed sign.
He just wants to shop like everyone else.
It's behind us right here.
This pole dancer seems slightly oversized for the stage.
They just jump here, they just jump here.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
In a dumpster diving contest, who wins Bear or Raccoon?
He's good at that.
What are you doing?
It's like the loop.
Scratch it.
I know.
That's how funny it is.
Knowing how to fix a car, definitely scores points with the ladies, her buddy.
Oh my gosh.
Can she just honk at it?
Get down.
Hey, do you have a sign?
Forget the scary Black Bear stereotype.
This is their true personality.
Just leave me alone, I won't bug you.
Hey, get out of here.
Oh, you messed it that time.
Hey, you messed it that time.
Definitely the kind of unboxing nobody ever wants to do.
Baby like, next time put the water bowl down.
This is too much work.
Go stand.
It's a birthday.
Oh my gosh.
I'm gonna put another bag in something.
Is that good?
What?
Is that?
Come on, let's go.
Zelda!
Come here.
Well, lucky for that dog.
North American Black Bear's prefer avoiding fights.
Oh my gosh, he's gonna die.
Zelda!
Come here.
Hi.
Hi, cutie.
Why you so cute?
Oh, he coming.
Oh my god, they're so cute.
Any of you brave enough to square up with a bear like this guy?
He smells like...
He smells Aryans.
Guys, he's in my car.
Hey.
Shit.
Now we understand why honeycombs are so high and bears still get them.
Go on now.
Go on now, boo.
Hey, hey, hey.
Go on now.
Go on, boo.
Go on.
Hey.
Go on, boo.
Hey, hey, hey.
Go on now.
Go on, boo.
Go on.
Hey.
You see?
Come on.
But look at this.
Bear be like, chill.
I just wanted to ask for directions.
What?
Bear be like this.
Bear be like...
Hey there.
That's her.
Watch out!
Watch out.
If you get caught, don't deny it.
The evidence is right there, buddy.
Oh, he's in here! They're caught a bit on the way!
Seems like Halloween is free pumpkin season for bears.
Ah, are they?
Dude, get good there.
Naughty kids, when they see the police, be like.
Here bear!
You mother!
Oh my god, he has the beer!
Someone thought the real car was just a life-size toy.
Oh my god, don't miss the next hilarious bear adventures.
Bye!